https://www.bodyzone.com/privacy-policy/

What This Privacy Policy Covers
This policy covers how BodyZone, LLC treats personal information that BodyZone, LLC collects and receives in connection with its public Web site as well as its membership Web site, BodyZone.com. Personal information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, e-mail address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available.
Information Collection and Use
BodyZone, LLC collects personal information when you register with BodyZone.com, our membership Web site including Posture Practice and other Posture Professionals, including Certified Posture Exercise Professionals (CPEPs), and when you visit BodyZone, LLC’s public Web site.
When you register with BodyZone, LLC we ask for information such as your name, e-mail address, birth date, gender, zip code, occupation, industry, and personal interests. Once you register with BodyZone, LLC and sign in to BodyZone.com, you are not anonymous to us.
BodyZone, LLC automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, BodyZone, LLC cookie information, and the page you request.
Information Sharing and Disclosure
BodyZone, LLC does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies except when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:
When we respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims; or
When we believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of BodyZone, LLC’s terms of use, confidentiality pledge and standards or as otherwise required by law.
Cookies
BodyZone, LLC may set and access cookies on your computer.
Cookies are files or pieces of information that may be stored in your computer’s hard drive when you visit a Web site.  This file or piece of information allows a user to move quickly and easily around our Web site and is used to identify returning users.  We also use a cookie to track a user’s sessions.  We use this information to find out what site features are most popular so we can develop our Web site and content in light of our analysis of people’s usage.
The use of cookies is an industry standard and done on most Web sites.
We do not, however, use cookies to retrieve involuntary information about your computer.
Accordingly, if you would prefer, you can set up your browser to refuse cookies or to alert you to their presence and thereby allow you to remove them from your computer.
Confidentiality and Security
We limit access to personal information about you to staff who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide services to you or in order to do their jobs.
We take all reasonable precautions to keep your personal information secure and we have put in place physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to protect personal information about you.
Links to other Web sites
The BodyZone.com public Web site and our membership Web site, BodyZone.com,  contain links to other Web sites; however, we are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites and do not make any representation as to the existence, sufficiency, accuracy or completeness of their Web sites or privacy policies.
Changes to this Privacy Policy
Due to changes in legislation and best practice or enhancements to functionality and content on BodyZone, LLC’s public Web site, BodyZone.com, we may update this privacy policy. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary e-mail address or by placing a prominent notice on our public Web site and BodyZone.com, and accordingly you should check here from time to time.
Questions and Suggestions
If you have questions or suggestions, please contact us at BodyZone, LLC. Attention: Privacy Officer, 3000 Old Alabama Road, Suite 119-352, Alpharetta, GA 30022.
Recent News
AARP Interviews Posture Expert
Hunched posture isn’t just for geriatrics any more. The implications of tech... View Article
© 2000–2020 BodyZone.com, All Rights Reserved. Terms & Use &bullet Privacy
